5apps.com 2019-05-30

# Privacy Policy | 5apps | 5apps

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes how AppCache Ltd ("5apps", "we", "us", "our") stores and processes personal data.

### What we collect and how we use it

#### Information you provide to us

  1. **Account/login information** , such as username (does not have to be a real name) and e-mail address (no discrimination of hosts), is used to facilitate account creation, authentication, and authorization. We may use your email address to contact you in regards to your account and the services it is signed up for. Additionally, you can subscribe and unsubscribe to product updates and such on our website, using this same email address. In order to manage your email preferences, please visit your [account settings page](https://5apps.com/account/settings).

  2. **Billing information** is required only when subscribing to a paid plan, or making a one-time payment for a service. We may collect credit/debit card details, or information related to other payment methods, in order to facilitate payments. Optionally, you can provide invoicing information, such as company name and address, and VAT ID, which will be printed on your invoices. Billing information will also be used for our bookkeeping and accounting.

  3. **Developer information** , such as developer/company name and email addresses may be provided by you per app hosted on 5apps Deploy, in order to be shown on public app pages, in app store entries, etc..

  4. **Support information** , such as information you provide when reporting a problem with our services, request support from us, or otherwise correspond with us, will be used to provide such support and investigate the problem at hand.

  5. **Publicly accessible data** , i.e. public profile information from connected sites, such as GitHub, GitLab and Bitbucket, will be used to improve your experience by for example pre-filling your username, or automatically importing your public SSH keys.

#### Information we collect automatically

  1. **Browser information** , such as browser type, IP address, language, device type, and operating system, will be used to improve the quality of our services and enhance your experience.

  2. **Usage information** , such as information about your interactions with our website and services, including pages visited, actions taken, features used, and the date and time of such interactions, are stored without personal identifiers, and used to improve our website and services. We (always have and always will) respect your browser's tracking configuration, namely [DNT (Do Not Track) headers](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Do_Not_Track). If you signal your preference to not have this data collected, it will never enter our database.

Please note: we do not use any external analytics services for automatically collected browser and usage data, so it is never leaked to bad actors, which may track you across the Internet for advertising and surveillance purposes.

### Exporting or deleting your data

You can request a machine-readable copy of your personal data from us. Please contact us via email to [support@5apps.com](mailto:support@5apps.com).

If you wish to delete your data, just head to your [account settings](https://5apps.com/account/settings) and use the button at the bottom of the page to cancel your account. Your data will be deleted automatically. However, we may retain a few necessary bits like e.g. invoicing information for our legally required bookkeeping.

### Data Storage

5apps uses third party vendors and hosting partners ("data processors") to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run our services. Although 5apps owns the code, databases, and all rights to the 5apps application, you retain all rights to your data.

We have so-called Data Processing Agreements with all our partners in order to ensure your privacy, according to the European Union's [General Data Protection Regulation](https://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/?uri=uriserv:OJ.L_.2016.119.01.0001.01.ENG&toc=OJ:L:2016:119:TOC).

### International data transfer

To facilitate 5apps’ global operations, the company may transfer and access data about 5apps customers from around the world. This privacy policy shall apply even if 5apps transfers data about customers to other countries.

### Sharing personal information with 3rd parties

Personally identifiable information we collect is solely used to provide our services, and is never shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes.

In the event of a proposed merger, acquisition, financing, sale of assets or in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy, receivership or other change of control, your personal data may be disclosed to a successor or assignee as part of our business assets. In such a case, you will be notified _in advance_ about the change of ownership or control, and will be able to have your data deleted before it would be shared.

### Disclosure

5apps may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service. Any requests have to comply with all legal requirements in the Netherlands, before we consider disclosure.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from our server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are required to log in to 5apps services. We do not store any personal data in cookies, and we solely use them to keep you logged in for a certain amount of time.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

5apps may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your 5apps account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Contacting Us

Any questions about this privacy policy or our practices in relation to your data in general may be addressed to [support@5apps.com](mailto:support@5apps.com).
